<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nathan Daeila - Technical Blog</title><link>http://localhost:1313/</link><description>Recent content on Nathan Daeila - Technical Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>100 Days of Learning Chinese: Product Breakdown of Duolingo</title><link>http://localhost:1313/blog/post-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/post-3/</guid><description>&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;I want to spend a year in Shenzhen,&amp;rdquo; I mentioned to my friends, with no reasonable explanation. To make my goal a reality, I decided to learn Mandarin Chinese, the primary language in Shenzhen, China. I quickly realized learning Chinese is difficult - the Chinese character set, Hanzi, is different from the English alphabet, in that the symbols illustrate meanings instead of representing phonetic sounds. I searched on Google for the best way to learn Chinese, and the first result was &lt;em>Duolingo&lt;/em>, an application that I initially heard about from Social Media. Duolingo is instantly recognizable for its mascot, a green, pudgy owl, now celebrated as a TikTok celebrity and familiar to many teenagers and adults.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Oxygen - Fixing the Nursing Shortage</title><link>http://localhost:1313/blog/post-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/post-2/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the heart of the University of Washington&amp;rsquo;s Annual DubHacks Hackathon, a seed of an idea took root, stemmed from a global issue in healthcare that hits my family close to home. My name is Nathan Daeila, and along with my colleague Ben Price, we set out on a journey not just to develop an application but to create a meaningful solution to a critical problem facing our healthcare system: the nursing shortage. This narrative isn&amp;rsquo;t about pitching an app; it&amp;rsquo;s about sharing our journey, our challenges, our intentions, and everything else that went into making &lt;em>Oxygen&lt;/em> a reality.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Welcome to My Tech Blog Journey!</title><link>http://localhost:1313/blog/post-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/post-1/</guid><description>&lt;h5 id="hello-and-welcome">Hello and Welcome!&lt;/h5>
&lt;p>I am Nathan, and I am thrilled to introduce you to my new blog. Here, I&amp;rsquo;ll be merging my passion for technology with my professional journey, aiming to create a space that&amp;rsquo;s both informative and engaging.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Search Result</title><link>http://localhost:1313/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/search/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="nathan-daeila">Nathan Daeila&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="product-manager--ischool-student">Product Manager &amp;amp; iSchool Student&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="university-of-washington-seattle">University of Washington, Seattle&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>I am Nathan Daeila, an aspiring Product Manager driven by a vision where every challenge is a stepping stone to innovation. Starting in the tech world as an IT intern during a global chip shortage, I quickly learned that when resources are scarce, creativity must flourish. Repairing computers and laptops was just the beginning; I soon found myself automating tasks in the IT department, paving my way to a role as a Systems Administrator.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="contact-me">Contact Me&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Welcome to Daeila.com! I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled that you&amp;rsquo;ve taken the time to visit my website.
Whether you have questions, feedback, or just want to say hello, I&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you.
Your thoughts and ideas are important to me, and I&amp;rsquo;m here to assist you in any way I can.
Please don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to reach out, and I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best to respond promptly.
Thank you for connecting with me, and I look forward to engaging with you!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Element</title><link>http://localhost:1313/element/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/element/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is going to be my resume.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="elements">Elements&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>A paragraph looks like this — Globally incubate standards compliant channels before scalable benefits. Quickly
disseminate superior deliverables whereas web-enabled applications. Quickly drive clicks-and-mortar
catalysts for change before vertical architectures. Credibly reintermediate backend ideas for cross-platform
models. Continually reintermediate integrated processes through technically sound intellectual capital.
Holistically foster superior methodologies. Check out &lt;a href="https://daeila.com"




 target="_blank"
 


>Daeila.com&lt;/a>
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My Resume</title><link>http://localhost:1313/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/resume/</guid><description>&lt;div style="text-align: center;">&lt;a
 href="http://tinyurl.com/ndaeila-resume"
 class="btn btn-primary text-white"
 
 target="_blank" rel="noopener"
 
 >Download Resume&lt;/a
>
&lt;/div></description></item></channel></rss>